I put my event on the day of the Libertadores final
good gill
then you don't want to take Pau right
and today is the day
calm hand
cocoa trophy
limited edition panettone show
now it's time for the crowd to arrive
sixty places
I sent a message to the staff there
I'm waiting to respond
then
I put this here to give 1 aesthetic
to give 1 break on this white wall here
so I improvised
these bars were already here too
is I'll give you another 10 minutes just and
starts after we talked yesterday
then three and a half i already have a bro appointment
O Cayon
saturday is a bad day man for us to go
I don't think I know if I got to tell you
it's bro it's complicated
he had
with his father to watch the Palmeiras game
guy they are going to another city i play today see final
so there's 1 guy canceling bro is
03:26 there are 3 more people arriving by shopping mall
and now you can't wait any longer
I'm going to start with these guys anyway.
I'm going to do my best for these guys who got here.
that we go
here bro
now we are in our safe break
six people here bro
but we're going to take a safe break
I thought you weren't going to come because of the football bro
I had a client to answer then I said so bro
but I'll tell you the real thing so we'll close an hour
because it's the following we
go after knowledge bro
then no one will take us
i.e.
we will take a step back
but for us to give a four
five steps is
otherwise it just ends up replicating
we think we are not worth
degree of comparison
what is the social network
that makes us frustrate
because we just look at each other
is the way he positions himself and communicates
because it must have equal to him
or better than him
a lot that doesn't know how to position itself and communicate
just that doesn't have to fit
i need to be me
people are seeing value in you and not price
only you're putting price in your place and not value
me
Let's get out of here
Word to your mother
I made 1 investment
only 5 people came
okay there I failed
look there guys
softness
snack for general there
salty new bro
croissant
1 lot of things
all ours
eat hand
O Claudia
has snack
you want snack
1 lot of party snack left